‎Hayato's voice
‎broke the sound barrier again.
‎Yota's been acting strange
‎ever since the sports festival.
‎SPORTS FESTIVAL
‎And he was in such good spirits.
‎SPACING OUT - KARAOKE
‎It's like his mind is elsewhere.
‎SCUTTLING AWAY - THE HALLWAY
‎And Miki seems to be avoiding him too.
‎Did something happen between them
‎that day after school?
‎POKE POKE
‎-Miki.
‎-What?
‎STOP THAT
‎-How you doing?
‎-Huh?
‎CRINGE
‎Why do you ask?
‎She sucks at this.
‎Just so you know,
‎I'm not "not" fine, okay?
‎I'm just a little sleepy.
‎EEK
‎Yeah? Well, that's good then.
‎Miki's been acting strange
‎ever since the sports festival.
‎And she was in such good spirits.
‎What happened?
‎She's making that grim face again.
‎Did something happen with Yota
‎when they were on clean-up duty?
‎Yota.
‎GLIDE
‎Koyun? What's up?
‎Well...
‎How you doing?
‎(TRIES TO) SMILE
‎PFFT - HUH?
‎She sucks at this.
‎Shall we step outside?
‎Miki found out.
‎What? Do you mean...
‎Did you tell her?
‎No, it kind of just slipped
‎based on my behavior.
‎If I'd have just kept it together,
‎she wouldn't have found out.
‎She wasn't giving off any signs
‎that she'd noticed or anything.
‎For a moment, I was actually hoping
‎she'd just get the message already.
‎I said I was fine with the way things are.
‎I really should learn
‎to make my mind up, hey?
‎But Miki already thinks highly of you.
‎If she knows you like her now,
‎she might start to feel the same way.
‎I don't think she will.
‎Miki's only ever seen me as a friend.
‎Ever since middle school.
‎At best, her best friend.
‎I hope I am.
‎And honestly, I'm fine with that.
‎Or at least I thought I was.
‎She knows how you feel about her now,
‎but that doesn't mean she'll suddenly
‎hate you or try to cut ties with you.
‎It must be that she just doesn't know
‎how to handle this right now.
‎Miki cares about the people around her.
‎She won't do anything reckless.
‎You're right.
‎Which is why I don't think I can let
‎things stay as ambiguous as they are.
‎Koyun. I...
‎I'm going to put an end to this.
‎EPISODE 14
‎BOMBSHELL
‎I think Yota likes me...
‎I can't exactly talk to Minato,
‎or anyone, really, about this.
‎Even if it's all in my head,
‎or even if it's all actually real...
‎If I talk to someone about it,
‎that'll just hurt Yota.
‎And what about Koyun?
‎If Koyun likes Yota, then...
‎Then I end up hurting two people!
‎Check, please.
‎Yes! On my way!
‎Yo, Miki.
‎Did something happen at school again?
‎You've had this dreadful look
‎about you all day.
‎You could tell? I'm so sorry.
‎Go on, then.
‎Let's hear your complaints.
‎No, I don't have any complaints.
‎But it might be easier to talk to these
‎guys instead of the people at school.
‎Well...
‎I may have just found out that somebody
‎who I thought was a friend
‎may actually have real feelings for me.
‎What do you think I should do?
‎Should I pretend like I haven't noticed
‎and just go about my life as usual?
‎Or maybe I should avoid them...
‎I don't know what to do.
‎DAMAGE
‎-Young love.
‎I'd probably feel flattered,
‎so long as I didn't hate the person.
‎In fact, if I found out a girl liked me,
‎that'd probably prompt me
‎to go on and ask her out myself.
‎Really?
‎But what if things go wrong?
‎Then you've lost a friend
‎in addition to a romantic partner.
‎Yeah, but I still hang out with my exes.
‎We grab food like nothing's happened.
‎Man, I don't think I could do that.
‎As you get older, you get more and more
‎of those fuzzy sorts of relationships.
‎Speak for yourself.
‎Is this friend of yours a boy or a girl?
‎It's a boy.
‎Then I'm not so sure.
‎When it's unrequited love from someone
‎you can't physically beat in a one-to-one,
‎it's best to nip that shit in the bud.
‎Based on my experience in battle with men,
‎you really need to have yourself a weapon.
‎Who hurt you?
‎GROANS
‎A jilted girl and a jilted guy
‎are two very different things.
‎He's not the type to fly into a rage,
‎so I think I'll be fine in that regard.
‎Well, things would be much easier
‎if you ended up with feelings for him too.
‎Feelings for him too...
‎When I'm with Yota...
‎I feel like myself,
‎and we always have a good time.
‎I'm sure Yota feels the same way.
‎We are each
‎a cozy place of warmth for the other.
‎Friends on equal footing.
‎How I wish that were the case...
‎CAMERA ROLL
‎What if I weren't a girl?
‎What if I weren't
‎a potential love interest?
‎Would we have gotten as close as we have?
‎Would he still have treated me
‎just as nice?
‎I want Yota to see me
‎not as a girl, not as a love interest,
‎but as a human being worthy of friendship.
‎INCOMING CALL - NINE AUDIO
‎Minato?
‎Hello?
‎Hello. Are you free to talk?
‎Yeah. Are you out right now?
‎Yeah. I'm on a walk with Ponta.
‎Little Raccoon-sky?
‎I just told you his name's Ponta.
‎What's up?
‎Not much, really.
‎I was just out for a walk
‎when I got this itch to talk to someone.
‎What the heck?
‎Yeah, there's no real meaning
‎behind my call.
‎But sometimes people
‎just get the itch to talk to others.
‎Yeah. Mood.
‎But are you sure
‎you're so itching to talk to me?
‎Why's that?
‎Don't you have girls lining up...
‎MEMORIES OF MIDDLE SCHOOL
‎...to talk to you on the phone?
‎Is that what you think of me?
‎There's no one like that for me.
‎And even if there were, I'd reach out to
‎them with a talking point already in mind.
‎And you wouldn't for me?
‎Why would I?
‎It's not like that between us.
‎What's with the pause?
‎Does this disappoint you?
‎Not at all!
‎I'm sorry I made you sad.
‎Shut up, you!
‎I'm just kidding.
‎Oh, my gosh.
‎I'm out too, and you've got me
‎looking like a weirdo
‎who yells in bicycle parking lots.
‎Are you just on your way home?
‎A little late, no?
‎Yeah. I had work.
‎I'm getting on my bike now.
‎I'm heading home too.
‎Little Pon's tired and won't move.
‎-‎Pon-pooped.
‎-It's just Ponta.
‎Talk to you later.
‎Was I a good killer for time?
‎You were. Thanks.
‎And feel free to call me
‎if you ever feel the need to talk.
‎-I will.
‎-‎See you tomorrow at the wrap party.
‎For the cheer squad! Yakiniku!
‎Had you forgotten?
‎Make sure to come, okay?
‎Yeah. Thanks.
‎Good night.
‎I wonder how Miki actually feels
‎about Yota right now.
‎Does she see him as a friend,
‎like Amamiya?
‎How long have you known Minato?
‎Come with me.
‎Koyun. Are Yota and Minato
‎"different" for you?
‎Does she?
‎Wait...
‎How does Miki see Amamiya,
‎and how does Amamiya see Miki?
‎As friends? Best friends?
‎Or is it something more?
‎I wonder how Amamiya sees me...
‎Wait, who cares about me!
‎Either way,
‎I hope they're both back to normal
‎at the cheer squad wrap party tomorrow.
‎YAKINIKU - ALL YOU CAN EAT
‎MEAT
‎Well done on the sports festival!
‎Hey, Miki. You look good with short hair.
‎Never go with salt. Always marinade.
‎Maybe I should go short too?
‎They're not.
‎Miki normally hangs out
‎with the guys in our grade,
‎but today,
‎she won't stop talking to the seniors.
‎Is it because this is a special occasion?
‎Am I overthinking this?
‎And Yota hasn't even tried to move
‎from where he first sat down.
‎STARE
‎IN NO POSITION TO TALK
‎Koyuki. They're gonna burn.
‎-You are so right.
‎-‎Amamiya.
‎You look kind of cute today.
‎You're wearing glasses.
‎Hey, guys. Don't you think Amamiya
‎and Momoka have similar kind of outfits?
‎-Huh?
‎Stand next to each other.
‎HUH?
‎Wow, you look great together!
‎What a cute couple.
‎-Thankies!
‎-You flirt.
‎BARF
‎He's that kind of guy...
‎Wow, this is kind of embarrassing.
‎They'll start teasing you more
‎if you show that you'll get shy.
‎They'll lose interest
‎if you just go along with it.
‎Amamiya...
‎-You sly fox, you.
‎-You think so?
‎PLAYING DUMB
‎Koyun.
‎SILENCE
‎Hey, Koyuki.
‎I've been wondering...
‎Do you not really like Amamiya?
‎What? Why?
‎Well, I mean, it kind of looks that way...
‎No. Not at all. That's not true.
‎Truly. Not at all!
‎That actually makes me suspicious.
‎Is that really the impression I give?
‎Well, you don't "not" give it?
‎I don't want that.
‎I'll have to rethink things.
‎No, there's no need to force the issue.
‎Mind if I sit here?
‎Momoka!
‎Boy, does my face feel hot.
‎I'm so embarrassed.
‎It sucks when they get carried away.
‎It's fine.
‎Because I actually really do like Amamiya.
‎Is it really that much of a surprise?
‎Do you mean as, like, a love interest?
‎Yep. That's right.
‎And so I was really happy
‎when they said we looked great together.
‎How nice...
‎But Amamiya likes...
‎What do you think, Koyun?
‎Huh? What do I think?
‎Do you think I should give it a shot?
‎That's for you to decide.
‎Who am I to tell you what to do?
‎I'm glad to hear that.
‎I thought if you were against it, Koyun,
‎then my hands would be completely tied.
‎Why me?
‎I mean, if the feeling's mutual,
‎there's no way
‎I could compete with you, right?
‎If the feeling's mutual?
‎-With who?
‎-‎Oh, no!
‎Oh, my. Are you playing coy?
‎No, no, no!
‎We all know who Amamiya likes.
‎It's obviously you.
‎It's over...
‎We all know who Amamiya likes.
‎It's obviously you.
‎What?
‎Amamiya likes me?
‎You're faking it.
‎By that reaction?
‎You're clearly faking it.
‎Surely you know, Koyun.
‎You know how Amamiya feels about you.
‎Can you really not tell
‎when someone likes you?
‎Amamiya is just nice to everyone.
‎I'm not special.
‎No. If I'm being honest,
‎there are some things that come to mind.
‎But I have to tell myself I'm not special.
‎It's not just me.
‎He'd do it for anyone.
‎I have to tell myself this.
‎I pretend I don't see it,
‎and I turn the other way...
‎WHAT IF I'M WRONG?
‎WHAT IF I'M NOT?
‎WILL OUR RELATIONSHIP CHANGE?
‎FOR BETTER? FOR WORSE?
‎I run from it to protect myself.
‎Maybe somewhere in the back of my mind
‎I really do ask, "What if"?
‎But...
‎I wish it weren't her
‎who made me realize all this.
‎Glad to hear it.
‎I feel so relieved hearing that from you.
‎I'll do my best
‎to make sure he loves me back.
‎NO COMMENT
‎So scary...
‎Her methods are scary.
‎Those who wanna keep the party rolling,
‎we're moving to the riverbank.
‎-Yay!
‎-Let's see...
‎-Fireworks!
‎-Where are my shoes?
‎Looks like we were neighbors.
‎Yep.
‎Wait... Koyun?
‎And we have the same watch.
‎SEIZING UP - WHOA
‎Oh, no... He's going to get the wrong idea.
‎I have to think of a response...
‎WHISPER
‎It was dirt cheap, wasn't it?
‎It was. But it looks so expensive.
‎I thought the same thing.
‎If you don't say anything,
‎then neither will I. Deal?
‎My glasses were dirt cheap too.
‎I see.
‎What do I do?
‎I won't say anything,
‎or I'll be outed too.
‎This is so much fun.
‎I wish we could stay
‎in this dynamic forever.
‎That was close!
‎I thought I'd lost
‎the key to my shoe locker.
‎Azumi. Stay back.
‎Huh? Hey, why?
‎Are you going
‎to see the fireworks after this?
‎Yeah. And Miki and Tsukiko are going too.
‎That's good to hear.
‎We didn't get to talk much today,
‎seeing as our seats were so far apart.
‎I was hoping you'd come.
‎At this point,
‎it's probably safe to say I'm certain.
‎Wait, what do I do?
‎What do I do, what do I do?
‎TURN
‎Is that so...
‎Koyun! Where are you?
‎BA-BUMP - WHOOSH
‎Here I am!
‎ALL ALONE
‎Hey, you coming down, or what?
‎I'm fine. I'm just watching from up here.
‎Lies! You just can't
‎bring yourself to come down!
‎You can do it. See?
‎LIFT
‎-Here!
‎-Hey!
‎I'm scared! Put me down!
‎Yes, yes. Hold on a sec.
‎Was that a scream?
‎Yo!
‎Koyun and Yota and Tsukko!
‎Yuki. Did you hear a weird voice just now?
‎Oh, that?
‎I was looking out for Atagawa.
‎She looks really angry.
‎Isn't it a little early for sparklers?
‎Aren't they normally saved for last?
‎HMPH
‎It's always a good time for sparklers.
‎Well, this is true.
‎Wanna join us?
‎Don't mind if I do!
‎STARE - RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
‎Why am I positioned here?
‎Feels like I'm being watched.
‎There goes mine.
‎You're going down with me, Koyun.
‎BLOW
‎Stop that.
‎Mind if I join?
‎Can I sit here?
‎FLINCH
‎Did I do something wrong?
‎THUMP THUMP THUMP
‎-‎This is hilarious.
‎What kind of faces are those?
‎CRACKLE CRACKLE
‎BANG
‎-Wow!
‎-So cool!
‎Amazing!
‎Shall we see whose can last the longest?
‎Sure.
‎Our elbows are so close.
‎Mine's lit.
‎Smile.
‎SMILE
‎SEIZING UP
‎Cheers to a job well done!
‎-Cheers!
‎Miki.
‎This is yours, isn't it?
‎I found it on the ground.
‎Wait, what? That's my key chain.
‎Hey, you're right.
‎It's not attached to my keys.
‎Here.
‎Thank you.
‎Good on you for knowing it was mine.
‎Of course I'd know it's yours.
‎Hey, Miki.
‎Do you feel awkward being around me?
‎What?
‎You're such an open book.
‎No... I don't feel awkward...
‎I'm sorry.
‎Are you free for a little after this?
‎There's something I need to tell you.
‎Miki.
‎If only he weren't about to say
‎what he's going to say.
‎Then things could stay the same.
‎I like you.
‎What?
‎Well, shucks. Thanks.
‎He's dead serious.
‎That wasn't a joke,
‎and it wasn't flippant.
‎He's being serious.
‎I've liked you all along.
‎Ever since middle school.
‎What?
‎All this time? He's liked me?
‎I never planned on telling you.
‎But I couldn't hide it any longer,
‎and so I wanted to bring it to a head.
‎I want to put an end to this
‎and go back to being just friends.
‎I'm sorry to put you out like this.
‎He's usually so smiley and kind.
‎I've never seen him make this face before.
‎How could I make him
‎make a face like that?
‎I like him too.
‎I love him.
‎But it's not...
‎No.
‎What if I make a conscious effort?
‎Then I might see him in the same way.
‎Who else is going to love me
‎and accept me for who I really am?
‎If I can fall in love with someone
‎in the same way that they love me...
‎Won't that make me happy?
‎Yota.
‎But...
‎I'm sorry.
‎I just can't say yes...
‎It's not that I don't like you too...
‎...while my heart is so unsure.
‎I've just never
‎thought of you in that way.
‎Okay.
‎I don't know what to do.
‎Yeah. I know.
‎I'm sorry I've been avoiding you recently.
‎I didn't mean to hurt you.
‎It's okay. I know.
‎I'm sorry.
‎It's fine.
‎Thank you.
‎Why are you crying?
‎Subtitle translation by: Rychelle Brittain